<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="bluestahli_name">Blue Stahli</string>
    <string name="celldweller_name">Celldweller</string>
    <string name="gramatik_name">Gramatik</string>
    <string name="redhotcp_name">Red Hot Chili Peppers</string>
    <string name="woodkid_name">Woodkid</string>

    <!--Synopsis from http://www.bluestahli.com/site/about/-->
    <string name="bluestahli_bio">
        There is no such thing as a guilty pleasure in Bret\’s world, and the music of Blue Stahli
        borrows from an untold number of disparate genres. The resulting blend is aggressively
        beautiful, vividly cinematic, and, above all, fun. Whether by furious guitar riffs,
        infectious vocal hooks, slick dance-floor beats, or atmospheric electronics, Blue Stahli
        is hellbent on making an emotional connection with the listener.
    </string>
    <!--Synopsis from http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Music/Celldweller-->
    <string name="celldweller_bio">
        Celldweller\'s music is incredibly diverse and multifaceted, and is commonly described as
        a fusion of Heavy Metal, trance, drum and bass, dubstep, and industrial, with elements
        taken from many other heavy music genres. The project has also been classified as Nu Metal
        and gains its pride as one of the Ensemble Darkhorses of the genre. Celldweller\'s music has
        frequently appeared in television shows, movies, and video games, more prominently appearing
        in Dead Rising 2, Need for Speed, and the 3rd season of Killer Instinct.
    </string>
    <!--Synopsis from https://www.last.fm/music/Gramatik/+wiki-->
    <string name="gramatik_bio">
        In 2006, he and 2 of his friends, fellow MC\'s, released their debut hip-hop album as a
        group called 5th Element, which was critically acclaimed throughout the country as one of
        the best hip-hop albums in Slovenia. After the album, Gramatik felt hip-hop just wasn\'t
        enough, that he was limiting himself with doing only one genre while he enjoyed listening
        to so many of them so he started producing House, Techno, Breakbeat, Electro, Drum'n'Bass,
        basically any genre that he liked which was anything that evolved from Blues, Jazz, Soul
        and Funk, as those ''father genres'' were all embedded deep in his style, whatever he would
        do. He realized that to him, music is much bigger than a genre name and their specific
        categorization, it's all about embracing what moves you and rejecting what doesn't.
    </string>
    <!-- Synopsis from https://www.rollingstone.com/music/artists/red-hot-chili-peppers/biography-->
    <string name="redhotcp_bio">
        Formed in the wake of the L.A. punk scene, the Red Hot Chili Peppers combined funk and punk
        with macho, sexed-up lyrics. (One early track was called "Party on Your Pussy"). The result
        was a high-octane sound that made the quintet alt-rock favorites in the Eighties, then
        superstars in the Nineties. But as the Chili Peppers aged, their songs became more laid-back
        and lyrical, and the band went from flesh-baring firecrackers (a 1992 Rolling Stone cover
        featured them naked) to respected veterans.
    </string>
    <!--Synopsis from https://www.allmusic.com/artist/woodkid-mn0002814238/biography-->
    <string name="woodkid_bio">
        Stepping out from behind the camera, Yoann Lemoine became one of the few music video
        directors to embark on a recording career of his own, with a number of releases under the
        guise of Woodkid … His self-directed video for "Run Boy Run" won Lemoine an MVPA Award for
        Best Director of the Year, and a Grammy nomination for Best Music Video. His debut album as
        Woodkid, The Golden Age, arrived in March 2013. The album received largely enthusiastic
        reviews, and fared well commercially, rising to number two on the French album charts, and
        going Top Ten in Belgium, Germany, and Switzerland.
    </string>
</resources>